<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="fairway_popup_description">
        Tracking fairway hits in golf enables you to record the landing position of your tee shots.
        It allows you to choose if your shot landed to the left, right, or in the middle
        of the fairway. This provides valuable data for analyzing and improving your golf game.
        This information helps you to make informed decisions and refine their strategies for
        subsequent shots.</string>
    <string name="gir_popup_description">
        Tracking Greens in Regulation (GIR) you\'ll gain valuable insights into
        your game. By monitoring how often you reach the green in the prescribed number of
        strokes, you gain a deeper understanding of your performance. GIR statistics help you
        identify strengths, pinpoint areas for improvement, and make data-driven decisions for a
        more strategic and successful game. Whether you\'re a seasoned golfer or just starting out,
        tracking GIR adds precision to your golf journey.</string>
    <string name="penalties_popup_description">
        Tracking golf penalties can greatly improve your game. It helps identify recurring
        mistakes, enhances self-awareness, and leads to informed adjustments. Understanding your
        penalty patterns makes you a more strategic and confident player, reducing unnecessary
        strokes and boosting your overall performance on the course.</string>
    <string name="put_popup_description">
        Tracking your putting game in is crucial for success on the green.
        It provides essential data on the number of putts per round, helping you refine your
        accuracy and distance control. By monitoring your putting statistics, you can fine-tune
        your stroke, enhance your short game, and ultimately lower your scores.</string>
    <string name="put_type_popup_description">
        Tracking different types of putts offers invaluable insights. It helps you gain insights
        into what sort of puts that you typically struggle with or find success in. Choice of types
        are either:\n\n
        a) Long, Medium, Short and Tap-in length puts.\n
        b) Lag, Drain-able, Drill-able and Tap-in puts.\n\n
        You can choose whichever suits your needs the best!
    </string>
    <string name="placeholder_popup_description">
        This extended placeholder text serves as filler content to demonstrate the layout and
        design of a document, website, or application. It is devoid of meaningful information
        and exists only for temporary visual representation. Placeholder text plays a crucial role
        in allowing designers and developers to visualize the arrangement of elements, typography,
        and overall aesthetics before the actual content is integrated. It helps ensure that the
        final product meets design expectations</string>
    <string name="put_type_choice_popup_description">
        Tap-In Putts: very short putts, typically within a few inches of the hole.\n
        Drill-able Putts: putts that are short and straight, and golfers aim to "drill" them directly into the hole without much break or curve.\n
        Drain-able Putts: putts that have a good chance of going into the hole, with a bit more curve than a drain-able put.\n
        Lag Putts: Lag putts are long-distance putts where the primary goal is to get the ball close to the hole, rather than sink it. They are typically used to set up an easier second putt.\n\n
        Long Range Putts: Long range putts are putts taken from a considerable distance away from the hole. These putts require more strength and accuracy to reach the target.\n
        Medium Range Putts: Medium range putts are taken from a moderate distance from the hole, often requiring good precision and feel to sink them.\n
        Short Range Putts: Short range putts are typically taken from close to the hole but require focus to ensure accuracy and proper aim.
</string>
    <string name="setup_question_one">Would you like to track Fairway hits?</string>
    <string name="setup_question_two">Would you like to track Greens in reg?</string>
    <string name="setup_question_three">Would you like to track your penalties?</string>
    <string name="setup_question_four">Would you like to track puts?</string>
    <string name="setup_question_five">Would you like to track different types of puts?</string>
    <string name="setup_question_six">How would you like to categorize your puts?</string>
</resources>